#01 "Powerful Skill Set"
Aristocratic Society
Baronet
Viscount
Baron
Earl
Marquess
Duke
Librarian
Baron
Viscount
Earl
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Skill [Great Sage]
Tells the user everything about the world
(even the unexplained).
It tells me everything about the world.
Q: What's tomorrow's
weather forecast?
A: It'll be sunny!
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Noir
Wings
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Noir
Wings
————
Skills
Get Creative
Bestow
Editor
Life Points
Slow
Fast
LP Conversion
Skill
Stone Bullet
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Noir Stardia  LP.550
Skills [Great Sage]
Skill  [Get Creative] [Editor] [Bestow]
Skill  [LP Conversion] [Stone Bullet]
Noir Stardia
A few hours prior
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Discerning Eye
Have a peek into
information about any
living creature or object.
Noir Stardia  LP.950
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Skills [Great Sage]
Skill  [Get Creative] [Editor] [Bestow]
Skill  [LP Conversion] [Stone Bullet]
Skill  [Discerning Eye]
Noir Stardia  LP.650
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Emma Brightness  Lv.17
Species
Occupation
Skills
[Human]
[Librarian]
[Dual-Wielded Daggers (Grade C)]
[Wind Strike]
Skill
Small Boobs
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Needed to Get Creative          LP.30
Needed to Bestow to Emma  LP.50
Hero Academy        The Day of the Exam
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Dead Reaper Lv.99
Skill [Execution Slash]
Skill Any damage dealt to its enemy with the
Skill Scythe means Instant Death. Effect cannot
Skill be avoided without specific resistance.
Not to mention, if that Scythe hits me,
it's an insta-death for me.
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Skill [Execution Slash]
LP needed to delete: 4000
Noir Stardia
#02 "The Guild and the Receptionist"
Illustration: Shiratama